<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The Huffington Post | The Full Feed</title>
    <link>www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
    <description>News and blog articles from The Huffington Post</description>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/documents-teen-laid-out-p_n_5256686.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Minnesota Teen Laid Out Detailed Plan To Attack School: Documents]]></title>
      <author>David Moye</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/documents-teen-laid-out-p_n_5256686.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 20:00:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The 17-year-old Minnesota boy outlined his plan in a 180-page journal: kill his family, set a fire to divert first responders, then go to his school with bombs and guns and "kill as many students as he could," according to court documents.<br />
<br />
The planned attack in Waseca, a city of about 9,400 people about 80 miles south of Minneapolis, was halted this week when a concerned citizen became suspicious and called police. When authorities responded, they say they found guns, bombs and other materials — all allegedly amassed by a teenager working alone as he methodically plotted his steps and conducted experiments to refine his plan to inflict bloodshed before being killed by responding officers. "The bomb squad members were shocked by the amount of bomb making chemicals and components (the teen) had," court documents say. "Bomb squad members said they have never seen that much of some of those chemicals in one place."<br />
<br />
The teen was arrested this week and charged in juvenile court with multiple counts of attempted first-degree murder, possessing explosive or incendiary devices and criminal damage to property. Prosecutors in Waseca County filed a motion Friday asking that he be charged as an adult, according to documents first obtained by KTOE-AM.<br />
<br />
Police were not commenting Friday, and messages left with the teen's family were not returned. Friday was a planned staff training day at the junior high and high school building that was the target of the alleged plot, and students did not have classes.<br />
<br />
"I think there's a range of emotions right now. We're all disturbed," said school Superintendent Thomas Lee. While he said he's confident the threat is gone, emotions range from: "'Should we have seen this coming? Did we miss something?' to 'Wow, I really like this kid,' ... to 'Wow, this could have actually happened in our school and our town.'"<br />
<br />
Police have not released a motive, though court documents made public Thursday paint an image of a boy who idolized at least one of the gunmen in the Columbine school shooting.<br />
<br />
Lee said the reserved teenager was well-liked and had friends.<br />
<br />
According to court documents, the teen first planned to fatally shoot his mother, father and sister, then start a fire in a rural location to draw first responders away from the city.<br />
<br />
He then planned to go to the school and detonate two pressure cooker bombs filled with shrapnel near the cafeteria. Then, while the school liaison officer was helping injured students, he planned to shoot and kill him, documents say.<br />
<br />
From there, he wanted to "kill as many students as he could" by setting off pipe bombs and throwing Molotov cocktails, then shooting students as they rushed into the hall, the documents say.<br />
<br />
Authorities say the teen's 180-page journal outlines the elaborate plan, complete with his research on chemicals, which he knew by scientific name, shrapnel and blast radiuses.<br />
<br />
His first entry was made July 24. The overall plan hadn't changed much since, but the teen tweaked the materials, detonators and other items he planned to use and conducted experiments to find what would "provide the most flash, fire capability, and would cause the most deaths," documents say.<br />
<br />
In the journal, he also outlined steps that would get him to his goal, including getting a job so he could buy supplies, opening a PayPal account so he could buy items online, renting a storage unit and stealing weapons.<br />
<br />
Authorities believe he would have carried out his attack in the next couple of weeks if he hadn't been stopped.<br />
<br />
A tip led police to the boy's storage unit, which police say was rented by a friend's mother. There, they arrested the teen Tuesday, after finding him with bomb-making materials.<br />
<br />
In the boy's bedroom, investigators found seven firearms, ammunition and three bombs.  Between the boy's home and storage unit, they also recovered a massive amount of chemicals and bomb-making materials, including fuses and wires, bottles of smokeless powders, a ski mask, a trench coat and 60 pounds of ball bearings.<br />
<br />
The teen's next court date is May 12. He's being held at a juvenile prison in Red Wing.<br />
<br />
___<br />
<br />
Follow Amy Forliti on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/amyforliti]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1774057/thumbs/s-WASECA-HIGH-SCHOOL-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/poker-princess-molly-bloom-probation_n_5256621.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA['Poker Princess" Molly Bloom Gets Probation (PHOTOS)]]></title>
      <author>Michael McLaughlin</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/poker-princess-molly-bloom-probation_n_5256621.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 19:29:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — A woman dubbed the Poker Princess for her role hosting poker games for the rich and famous has learned prison isn't in the cards.<br />
<br />
Federal Judge Jesse Furman in New York City said Friday prison would be too harsh a punishment for 36-year-old Molly Bloom. Bloom pleaded guilty in December to charges she helped run underground games for Wall Street financiers and celebrities in rooms at The Plaza hotel. She's working these days for a clothing company in Hollywood, California. And she's writing a memoir.<br />
<br />
The judge says Bloom seemed contrite but he wanted to make sure nothing in her book would conflict with what she was saying at her sentencing. Bloom said it would not.<br />
<br />
Prosecutors did not seek a prison sentence, saying Bloom had a minor role in what was a Russian mob case.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/wedding-day-tornado_n_5256325.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Wedding Saves Bride And Groom From Deadly Tornado]]></title>
      <author>Taryn Hillin</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/wedding-day-tornado_n_5256325.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 19:03:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[When a tornado with 200 mph winds ripped through Mark Patterson's Arkansas home on April 27, he and his family were spared an almost certain death due to a strange but wonderful miracle. <br />
<br />
Instead of spending that Sunday night at home like they always do, Patterson and his fiancée were several towns away getting married.<br />
<br />
<strong>(Story continues after photo.)</strong><br />
<img alt="2014-05-02-notresized.jpg" src="http://images.huffingtonpost.com/2014-05-02-notresized.jpg" width="570" height="855" /><br />
<small><em>Credit: Melanie Russell of <a href="http://www.therussellphotography.com" target="_hplink">Russell Photography</a></em></small><br />
<br><br />
<br />
"There's a definite, 100 percent chance we would have been home," Patterson <a href="http://www.arkansasonline.com/news/2014/may/01/wedding-day-tornado-saved-our-lives/" target="_hplink">told the Arkansas Democrat-Gazette</a>. "No question about it. We wouldn't be alive."<br />
<br />
Patterson and his family live just outside <a href="http://www.kspr.com/news/local/faulkner-county-ef4-tornado-destroyed-328-homes/21051620_25772134" target="_hplink">Mayflower, Arkansas, where the recent EF4 tornado </a> destroyed an estimated 328 homes and killed 15 people statewide. <br />
<br />
Luckily, their wedding took place in Roland, Arkansas, where the couple and their three kids avoided danger. And in another twist of fate, April 27 wasn't always the date they had in mind; according to the report, Patterson says he and his fiancée first settled on April 26 but changed their minds. <br />
<br />
Now, instead of heading off to their honeymoon in Mexico, the couple is sorting through their <a href="http://www.arkansasonline.com/news/2014/may/01/wedding-day-tornado-saved-our-lives/" target="_hplink">home's wreckage,</a> hoping to find important sentimental items like photographs and family heirlooms. Luckily, they already found their two dogs, Daisy and Dixie, who both managed to survive the winds.<br />
<br />
Despite the damage, Patterson says he feels lucky and told the Arkansas Democrat-Gazette that when people ask him about his wedding day, he'll have the perfect answer.<br />
<br />
"I'll just say it saved our lives," he said. <br />
<br />
<em>Keep in touch! Check out HuffPost Weddings on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/HuffPostWeddings" target="_hplink">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/#!/HuffPostWedding" target="_hplink">Twitter </a>and <a href="http://pinterest.com/huffpostwedding/" target="_hplink">Pinterest</a>. Sign up for our newsletter <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/newsletter/weddings" target="_hplink">here</a>.</em><br />
 ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1773956/thumbs/s-TORNADO-WEDDING-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/i-should-kill-you-right-h_n_5256491.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA['I Should Kill You Right Here']]></title>
      <author>Andrew Hart</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/i-should-kill-you-right-h_n_5256491.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:42:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[The pro-Russia militants who stood guard at one of the tire-strewn checkpoints littering eastern Ukraine presented a fearsome picture on Friday morning, their faces wrapped in black ski masks and pistols tucked into their body armor. ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1774021/thumbs/s-PRORUSSIAN-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/louis-ck-testing-common-core-david-letterman_n_5255310.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Louis C.K. Continues To Knock Standardized Testing In 'David Letterman' Appearance]]></title>
      <author>Rebecca Klein</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/louis-ck-testing-common-core-david-letterman_n_5255310.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:41:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Louis C.K. took his complaints about standardized testing to late night television Thursday, telling David Letterman his two daughters were currently amid three days of "high-pressure" exams at their public schools. <br />
<br />
The appearance on "David Letterman" comes after the <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/04/28/louis-ck-common-core_n_5228947.html" target="_hplink">comedian knocked standardized testing and the Common Core State Standards</a> on Twitter this week. In the tweet, he sarcastically thanked the Common Core Standards for making his daughters cry and <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/01/common-core-louis-ck_n_5249712.html" target="_hplink">suggested the standards implementation process had been rushed in New York State</a>. He also posted photos of one of his <a href="https://twitter.com/louisck/status/460896591583670272/photo/1" target="_hplink">daughter's math homework</a>, musing, "Who is writig these? And why? [sic]"<br />
<br />
The comedian reiterated his confusion over his daughters' math homework -- aligned with the Common Core -- to Letterman Thursday. <br />
<br />
"I look at the problems, and it’s like, 'You know Bill has three goldfish. He buys two more. How many dogs live in London?'" he joked.<br />
<br />
The Common Core State Standards have been adopted in more than 40 states in an effort to make sure students across the country are being held to the same measure.<br />
<br />
<em>Louis C.K.'s comments about testing start at about 0:58 in the video above. </em> ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1773942/thumbs/s-LOUISCK-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/ben-affleck-counting-cards-casino_n_5256376.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Ben Affleck Kicked Out Of Casino For Counting Cards (REPORT)]]></title>
      <author>Stephanie Marcus</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/ben-affleck-counting-cards-casino_n_5256376.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:39:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Ben Affleck was allegedly <a href="http://www.tmz.com/2014/05/02/ben-affleck-hard-rock-casino-counting-cards-blackjack/" target="_hplink">kicked out of the Hard Rock Casino in Las Vegas </a>after security believed they caught him counting cards, TMZ reports.<br />
<br />
Sources told the website that the 41-year-old actor was in Las Vegas earlier this week with wife Jennifer Garner so the pair could spend some quality time together before he heads off to Detroit to film the new Batman movie. According to TMZ's sources, Affleck was playing blackjack at a high rollers' table when security suddenly "swarmed" him. <br />
<br />
RadarOnline reports that <a href="http://radaronline.com/exclusives/2014/05/ben-affleck-las-vegas-card-counting/" target="_hplink">Affleck was barred from playing shortly after 10 p.m. on April 28</a>, “due to moving his money with the count,” according to an alert from a local security firm acquired by Star magazine. The actor was allegedly using "perfect basic," which is a common term for introductory card counting, the alert stated. RadarOnline also reports that another alert was issued the next day to major casinos in the area claiming Affleck is “currently suspected of advantage play.”<br />
<br />
Affleck is no stranger to gambling and <a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-2012095/Ben-Affleck-lost-400k-movie-mogul-Ron-Meyer-Hollywood-poker-ring.html" target="_hplink">famously lost $400,000 to Hollywood hotshot Ron Meyer in 2011</a>. <br />
<br />
The actor, who also starred in the <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0184858/" target="_hplink">casino-heist movie "Reindeer Games,"</a> has reportedly been banned for life from playing blackjack at the Hard Rock Casino, according to TMZ's sources.<br />
<br />
Request for comment made to Affleck's rep has yet to be returned.  ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1773980/thumbs/s-BEN-AFFLECK-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/johns-hopkins-gang-rape-review_n_5256263.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins University To Review Why It Kept Quiet About Gang Rape Report]]></title>
      <author>Tyler Kingkade</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/johns-hopkins-gang-rape-review_n_5256263.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:36:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins University said Friday it will commission an independent review of the school's response to an alleged fraternity house gang rape, which students have charged in a federal complaint violated a campus security law.<br />
<br />
Johns Hopkins administrators knew Baltimore police were investigating the reported gang rape at the Pi Kappa Alpha fraternity in March 2013, but decided against informing the campus, <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/01/johns-hopkins-rape-complaint_n_5228116.html" target="_hplink">The Huffington Post reported Thursday</a>. Students have accused the university in a federal complaint filed in February of violating the Clery Act, a federal law that mandates the reporting of certain campus crime and security issues, by failing to issue a warning as students continued attending parties at the fraternity.<br />
<br />
Students<a href="http://www.wbaltv.com/news/report-johns-hopkins-university-did-not-report-alleged-rape-at-frat-house/25780872" target="_hplink"> gathered on Johns Hopkins' Baltimore campus</a> <a href="http://www.jhunewsletter.com/2014/05/01/administration-criticized-for-withholding-pike-gang-rape-allegations-52414/" target="_hplink">Friday afternoon demanding</a> more <a href="http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2014/05/02/hopkins-students-protest-over-alleged-sex-assault-response-jhu-president-to-order-independent-review/" target="_hplink">transparency in response</a> to the article.<br />
<br />
"The university was aware of an allegation of sexual assault that was made in March 2013," the school said in an announcement to the campus Friday. "The decision not to notify the university community in that case was made after considering relevant facts and legal requirements, and in consultation with the Baltimore police department, which was leading the investigation. After the incident, campus security continued to communicate with law enforcement authorities."<br />
<br />
Johns Hopkins President Ronald J. Daniels has ordered an independent review of the school's handling of incidents described in the complaint, the university said. "The university is committed to scrupulous self-examination, and the review will begin immediately," the school's statement said.<br />
<br />
<a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/01/johns-hopkins-rape-complaint_n_5228116.html" target="_hplink">The Clery Act complaint also accused Johns Hopkins</a> administrators of dissuading students from filing formal reports of sexual assault, and of telling one victim if she went through a university adjudication, she could not go to police.<br />
<br />
The university's statement said its new efforts to address sexual violence include expanded training programs for students and employees, a 24-hour "safeline" for victims of sexual assault staffed by trained counselors, and plans for a website on sexual violence prevention. ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1773916/thumbs/s-JOHNS-HOPKINS-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/first-chaos-then-clarity_n_5256460.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[First Chaos, Then Clarity]]></title>
      <author>Chris Greenberg</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/first-chaos-then-clarity_n_5256460.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:36:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[C.J. Paul has seen a lot through the years. As manager for his brother Chris' basketball and business interests, he was there when the Hornets relocated to Oklahoma City for the two years after Hurricane Katrina struck New Orleans. He was there when the NBA took control of the team a few years later, after owner George Shinn could no longer afford it. And he was there when former commissioner David Stern vetoed his brother's trade to the Lakers and "a week later you're going to the Clippers," he remembers with a smile and a shake of his head.<br />
 ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1774010/thumbs/s-CLIPPERS-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/lauren-a-rothman/fashion-whip-washington-red-carpet-white-house-correspondents-dinner_b_5254031.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Fashion Whip: Celebrating Washington's Own Red Carpet, AKA The White House Correspondents' Dinner]]></title>
      <author>Lauren A. Rothman</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/lauren-a-rothman/fashion-whip-washington-red-carpet-white-house-correspondents-dinner_b_5254031.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:34:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<em>Fashion Whip is a political style column in the Huffington Post by Lauren A. Rothman, inspired by Lauren's experience as the founder of <a href="http://www.styleauteur.com" target="_hplink">Styleauteur</a>, a style and fashion consulting firm.</em><br />
<br />
Locals will have Hollywood royalty in their backyard this weekend. Saturday is Washington's big day to dress up, and every year the <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/news/white-house-correspondents-dinner/" target="_hplink">White House Correspondents' Dinner</a> festivities get even the most slovenly dressers into a tie or tux. This is the media's weekend to celebrate and many will push through the daily news cycle as they attend celebrity-studded parties around town.<br />
<br />
<img alt="amy poehler whcd 13" src="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1773985/thumbs/o-AMY-POEHLER-WHCD-13-570.jpg?8" /><br />
<center><em>Amy Poehler at the 2013 White House Correspondents' Dinner.</em></center><br />
<br />
Many of TV and film's biggest stars will be in attendance but even the flashiest of celebs tone it down on DC's red carpet. Actors and the people they emulate on TV and in movies will mingle at brunches and cocktail parties. You may see <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/news/julianna-margulies/" target="_hplink">Julianna Margulies</a> from <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/09/27/the-good-wife-daniel-lawson-costume-designer_n_3997592.html" target="_hplink">"The Good Wife"</a> alongside someone who really is a good wife, and America's favorite television president, <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/news/tony-goldwyn/" target="_hplink">Tony Goldwyn</a> from <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/10/03/scandal-costume-designer-lyn-paolo_n_4029659.html" target="_hplink">"Scandal"</a>, may pose for pics with President <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/news/barack-obama/" target="_hplink">Obama</a>. While this event always has a best-dressed list, politicos and press superstars take their own turns to shine at the Washington Hilton.<br />
<br />
Some famous on air-personalities enjoy fashion and style but, on the whole, this is an industry that doesn't do <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/tag/spray-tans" target="_hplink">spray tans</a>, teeth whitening, or borrowed jewels. You're more likely to see people getting their makeup done at a Nordstrom counter and a blowout in Georgetown, than ushering a glam squad into their home.<br />
<br />
<img alt="obama laughing whcp 13" src="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1773994/thumbs/o-OBAMA-LAUGHING-WHCP-13-570.jpg?4" /><br />
<center><em>President Barack Obama at the 2013 White House Correspondents' Dinner.</em></center><br />
<br />
Just what, you might ask, is the key difference between a Hollywood red carpet and the White House Correspondents' Dinner? This presidential send-up is traditionally attended by the District's old-school press royalty. Washington's most valuable currency is power and here that nest egg grows with experience. Many wear the same shoes for 12 hours and get frustrated when dresses and skirts don't have pockets -- it's not unusual for me to be tasked at the last minute with finding clutches (with optional straps, of course) to accommodate reading glasses, multiple cell phones, and lipstick. The DC vanguard expects comfort and convenience from their ensemble even in the dressiest of circumstances.<br />
<br />
Most celebrities visiting the nation's capital this weekend will be dressed in borrowed designer duds, accessories, and the latest trend in shoes as they are photographed coming and going. They will dress to impress and continue their personal branding through this unique extension of the recent awards season, looking to land an endorsement deal to become the next face of a fragrance, makeup empire, or retailer.<br />
<br />
<img alt="savannah guthrie whcp 13" src="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1773988/thumbs/o-SAVANNAH-GUTHRIE-WHCP-13-570.jpg?8" /><br />
<br />
<center><em>Savannah Guthrie at the 2013 White House Correspondents' Dinner.</em></center><br />
<br />
Meanwhile, the press core is a group that buys their own formal attire, sometimes on sale and usually off the rack. I have certainly helped DC power players source unique, custom, and couture gowns but, for this event, expect slits instead of cutouts, understated lace in place of bold patterns, higher necklines and peplum waists. Red carpet red is always popular and a sea of black makes it easy to blend in at the affectionately referred to "Nerd Prom."<br />
<br />
The best way to add District sparkle and blur the line between celeb and politico? Rent the Runway -- a well-kept secret (totally worth bragging about) that will help any party-goer feel like Cinderella -- or First Lady <a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/news/michelle-obama/" target="_hplink">Michelle Obama</a> -- and fit right in!<br />
<br />
<em><strong>See what stars wore last year:</strong></em><br />
<HH--236SLIDEEXPAND--294360--HH> ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1108910/thumbs/s-WHITE-HOUSE-CORRESPONDENTS-DINNER-RED-CARPET-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/lois-metzger/ray-harryhausen-an-apprec_b_5208559.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Ray Harryhausen: An Appreciation]]></title>
      <author>Lois Metzger</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/lois-metzger/ray-harryhausen-an-apprec_b_5208559.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:31:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<a href="http://images.huffingtonpost.com/2014-05-02-Harryhausensnakewoman.jpeg"><img alt="2014-05-02-Harryhausensnakewoman.jpeg" src="http://images.huffingtonpost.com/2014-05-02-Harryhausensnakewoman-thumb.jpeg" width="224" height="225" /></a><br />
Photo credit:  The Ray & Diana Harryhausen Foundation<br />
<br />
Ray Harryhausen, the stop-motion animation genius who learned his craft from Willis O'Brien, the man who invented King Kong, died a year ago, on May 7, 2013, at the age of 92.  Creating special effects entirely by hand and without the help of computers, Harryhausen directly inspired Steven Spielberg, George Lucas, Peter Jackson, James Cameron and Tim Burton.  Not to mention the special effect he had on the rest of us, the movie-goers.<br />
<br />
I grew up with Harryhausen's films and still get a kick out of them:  <em>The 7th Voyage of Sinbad</em>, <em>Jason and the Argonauts</em>, <em>Clash of the Titans</em>.  By today's standards, these movies aren't scary, but they were certainly scary to me.  I can remember the first time I saw <em>Jason and the Argonauts</em> -- when a giant statue came to life and merely turned its head, I nearly jumped out of my seat.  Even more amazing, it scared me more the second time I saw it.  In <em>7th Voyage</em>, a woman was put into a giant vase with a serpent.  She was transformed into a half-woman, half-snake; her upper body was still female, but she had an extra pair of arms, and the rest of her body was that of a snake.  She started to dance; I got completely freaked out.  She seemed to be enjoying it!<br />
<br />
Harryhausen was the author of several books, which he co-authored with Tony Dalton:  <em>An Animated Life</em> (foreword by Ray Bradbury), <em>The Art of Ray Harryhausen</em>, <em>A Century of Stop-Motion Animation</em>.  Basically, stop-motion animation is the art of creating the illusion of movement in an inanimate object.  You take a model of a creature -- say, a dinosaur.  You film a frame of the dinosaur, then walk to the dinosaur, move the dinosaur a fraction of an inch (a change too small to see with the naked eye), walk back to the camera and film another frame, then walk back to the dinosaur, move it again and repeat, repeat, repeat.  Because there are 24 frames for one second of film, you move the dinosaur 24 times for only a single second of animation.  This means 1,440 movements for every minute of film, and 86,400 for a full hour.  As Harryhausen said, "The animator walks miles in a day, back and forth... patience is essential."<br />
<br />
Even more of a special effect than the fact that these creatures seem to live and breathe is the emotion that Harryhausen gave them.  He put himself into his creations, making sure each had "a mind and a soul."  "I have always wanted audiences to feel sorry for my creatures when they are being destroyed," he wrote.  His creatures weren't inherently evil, he explained, unless something else was controlling them.  I can remember getting upset when the dragon died at the end of <em>7th Voyage</em>.  It was only protecting the magician's lair, a loyal guard.  Its death was kind of sad and slow, too, like Camille's.<br />
<br />
Harryhausen brought to life creatures that are familiar to us, such as baboons, bees, crabs, lions and chickens (though sometimes they were gigantic or two-headed or both), and magical beings from mythology (dragons, harpies, Cyclops) and animals from the past (dinosaurs, saber-toothed tigers).  Sometimes he invented something completely original, such as the half-woman, half-snake with four arms.  He referred to these as "creatures from the mind."  He said, "Deep down I knew the images couldn't be real but in the back of my mind I hoped they were."<br />
<br />
They will live on in many people's minds.  Which is even better. ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1464944/thumbs/s-US_UK_CA-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/nathan-white/net-neutrality_b_5256423.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Net Neutrality and the Future of the Internet]]></title>
      <author>Nathan White</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/nathan-white/net-neutrality_b_5256423.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:29:13 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><b>What is Internet Neutrality?</b></p><br />
<br />
<p>Internet Neutrality, or Net Neutrality, is the principle that all data on the Internet should be transmitted the same regardless of content or origin. This means that currently, your Internet Service Provider (ISP) treats the relatively small amount of data required to check your email the same way it treats the large amount of data necessary to stream a video. Often, your ISP is the same entity as your cable company provider (Verizon, Comcast, Charter, etc.) If Net Neutrality didn't exist, your ISP would be free to change the speed at which you can access certain content, or block it all together. The process for selecting an Internet package might look like <a href="https://www.dvice.com/sites/dvice/files/styles/blog_post_media/public/images/net-neutrality.jpg?itok=KLxHII1n" target="_blank">this</a>.</p><br />
<br />
<p>The issue of Net Neutrality affects more than just the amount you might pay for access to the Internet. It has implications for the future of the Internet and the economies that rely on the Internet. For example, in 2004, MySpace was the dominant social networking site. If Net Neutrality did not exist in 2004, users who liked MySpace would pay for faster access to that site. As a result, the fledgling website created in a Harvard dorm room we now know as Facebook would have suffered comparatively slower speeds. Since the initial Facebook experience (like many start-ups) was subpar, it likely would not have become the economic giant we know today. In this scenario (without the existence of Net Neutrality), the launch of Google+ in 2011 could also have transpired very differently. Since it is backed by a billion-dollar corporation able to pay for faster access, Google+ could have rapidly dominated the social media market. The current practice of Net Neutrality has allowed a free and fair competition in the digital marketplace.</p><br />
<br />
<p>Net Neutrality also promotes American infrastructure development, which is vital to our national economic interests. In a similar way to the evolution of cell phone network speed in recent years (2g, 3g, LTE, etc.), Internet Service Providers compete for customers by expanding their networks and providing faster, better Internet connections. Without Net Neutrality, the economic incentive to improve infrastructure would be removed. In fact, it could manifest as a disincentive to infrastructure development and innovation, since ISPs could alternatively focus on encouraging users to pay more to access certain sites at current top speeds, while effectively "slowing down" or prohibiting access to others.</p><br />
<br />
<p><b>What happened to Net Neutrality?</b></p><br />
<br />
<p>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) has the authority to govern communications networks like broadband Internet under the 1996 Telecommunications Act.</p><br />
<br />
<p>In the 1990s, most Internet access came in over the phone lines and the law treated the Internet as a "telecommunication service." This meant that the rules that applied to the Internet were covered under Title II of the Telecommunications Act. Under Title II, the FCC had the authority to mandate Internet companies to treat all data equally. At that time, it was treated similarly to phone lines, where phone calls were received first-come, first-serve.</p><br />
<br />
<p>By 2002, residential Internet access was delivered by cable and it was called broadband. The FCC decided to regulate broadband as a Title I "information service." This was a controversial decision and lawsuits were filed. Ultimately, the Supreme Court ruled that the FCC had the final authority to determine how it would classify (and regulate) broadband Internet access. At the time, the court did not decide on the merits of Net Neutrality.</p><br />
<br />
<p>The Internet community continued to push and in 2005, the FCC adopted a set of openness principles designed to protect Net Neutrality. However in 2010, when the Commission moved to codify these guidelines, Verizon filed a lawsuit. Verizon argued that under Title I, the FCC did not have the legal authority to make these rules.</p><br />
<br />
<p>In January of this year, the Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia ruled in favor of Verizon. The court declared that the FCC could not use Title II rules to govern Title I broadband. As a result, the rules that would have protected Net Neutrality were stricken.</p><br />
<br />
<p><b>Why am I hearing that the FCC just killed Net Neutrality?</b></p><br />
<br />
<p>When the court issued its ruling in January, it didn't rule against Net Neutrality specifically. The court only said that FCC's legal rationale for the rules was invalid. The court even recognized FCC's authority under Section 706 (of the 1996 Telecommunications Act) to act on a case-by-case basis to promote broadband deployment. It was up to FCC to decide how to move forward.</p><br />
<br />
<p>Last week, the media began to report on FCC Chairman Tom Wheeler's new proposed rules. The specifics have not been released yet, but according to the news reports FCC will allow ISPs to negotiate individualized discriminatory deals with different websites and Internet services (like Netflix). Tiered Internet would exist with both the Internet services AND the ISPs broadband customers could be forced to pay for access and faster speeds.</p><br />
<br />
<p>The FCC says now that it would use its authority under Section 706 to ensure that the ISPs charged a "fair price" on these new tolls. The 5-person FCC is scheduled to vote on this proposal on May 15, 2014.</p><br />
<br />
<p>Some have suggested that the Chairman's proposed rules protect the Internet to the extent permitted by the court's ruling in January. That's not true. The FCC has better legal authority it could use, and the court's ruling recognized that. Instead of working to protect an Open Internet for real, Chairman Wheeler's compromised proposal would end Net Neutrality and represent a fundamental change in the nature of the Internet and its economies.</p><br />
<br />
<p><b>What can we do to get Net Neutrality back?</b></p><br />
<br />
<p>In 2002 the Supreme Court ruled that the FCC has the authority to classify broadband under the 1996 Telecommunications Act. The FCC can simply vote to reclassify broadband as a Title II "telecommunications service" and enact rules to protect Net Neutrality.</p><br />
<br />
<p><b>Why doesn't the FCC just reclassify?</b></p><br />
<br />
<p>That's a good question. President Obama claims to support Net Neutrality, as does the Chairman of the FCC, Tom Wheeler. Mr. Wheeler has enormous power and authority to lead the FCC toward the reclassification of broadband, or preside over Net Neutrality's funeral.</p><br />
<br />
<p><b>Who is Tom Wheeler?</b></p><br />
<br />
<p>Mr. Wheeler is a former lobbyist for the cable industry. He was previously the President of the National Cable Television Association and the CEO of Cellular Telecommunications &amp; Internet Association, and he has been inducted in to the Cable Television Hall of Fame and the Wireless Hall of Fame. Mr. Wheeler's immediate predecessor now works for the Carlyle Group, and a former FCC Chairman (who presided over the 2002 decision to classify broadband as Title I) is now a lobbyist for the cable industry. In addition to senior <a href="http://m.vice.com/read/former-comcast-and-verizon-attorneys-now-manage-the-fcc-and-are-about-to-kill-the-internet" target="_blank">leadership, staff</a> at the FCC routinely work for the industries they regulate.</p><br />
<br />
<p><b>What do Internet companies think about all this?</b></p><br />
<br />
<p>This is an uncomfortable subject for many companies because their economic interests do not match their publicly portrayed values. Websites and companies like Facebook, Google, and Netflix have all benefited greatly from Net Neutrality. However, now that these corporations are big enough to pay the ISPs for faster service, the end of Net Neutrality would severely inhibit their competition, effectively locking-in their market share in the Internet economy.</p><br />
<br />
<p><b>What can I do?</b></p><br />
<br />
<p>The FCC will meet to decide the future of the Internet and Net Neutrality on May 15, 2014. The next two weeks are critical for Internet users to participate in the process. Sign a <a href="http://act.rootsaction.org/p/dia/action3/common/public/?action_KEY=9726&amp;track=DP20140424&amp;tag=DP20140424" target="_blank">petition</a>, call your member of Congress, tweet, or organize your own <a href="http://www.freepress.net/resource/105981/how-lobby-your-elected-officials-net-neutrality-reclassification-and-internet" target="_blank">lobbying meeting</a>. </p> ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1464944/thumbs/s-US_UK_CA-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/foul-ball-camera-_n_5254270.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Foul Ball Makes TV Camera's Final Moments Amazing (VIDEO)]]></title>
      <author>Arman Walia</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/05/02/foul-ball-camera-_n_5254270.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:24:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[You might not want to use your best camera if you choose to film a baseball game from behind home plate. Just ask <a href="http://videodesignstudio.com/Video_Design_Studio/Blank.html" target="_hplink">Greg Horn of Video Design Studio</a>, he learned first-hand. Greg was filming a game in Flagstaff, Arizona when a foul ball completely demolished his camera. <br />
<br />
 (H/T <a href="http://bleacherreport.com/articles/2048595-foul-tip-smashes-camera-at-high-school-baseball-game?utm_source=facebook.com&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=programming-national" target="_hplink">Bleacher Report</a>)]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1772905/thumbs/s-BASEBALL-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/reboot-illinois/top-5-weirdest-laws-in-il_b_5247871.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[You Won't Believe These 5 Weird Laws in Illinois!]]></title>
      <author>Reboot Illinois</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/reboot-illinois/top-5-weirdest-laws-in-il_b_5247871.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:23:36 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Local<a href="http://rboot.co/R3YpJg" target="_blank"> laws reflect</a> the values of a community--what the residents think is most important for <a href="http://rboot.co/1n6XRgX" target="_blank">running a city or town </a>effectively and the kinds of things they do or do not want happening within their city limits. It seems that Illinoisans have some pretty specific ideas about what they <em>do not </em>want happening in their hometowns.<br />
<br />
Check out this list of the weirdest laws in Illinois. Can you think of any other weird<a href="http://rboot.co/1n6Y3wC" target="_blank"> laws in your city or town</a>?<br />
<br />
<a href="http://www.rebootillinois.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/Weird-laws-in-Illinois1-e1398869437261.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-7589" src="http://www.rebootillinois.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/Weird-laws-in-Illinois1-e1398869437261.jpg" alt="Weird laws in Illinois" width="630" height="1244" /></a><br />
<br />
&nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp;<br />
<h1><span style="color: #0000ff;"><a href="http://rboot.co/1kpDgBP" target="_blank"><span style="color: #0000ff;">NEXT ARTICLE: Take our poll: Is it time for term limits in Illinois?</span></a></span></h1><br />
&nbsp;<br />
<br />
<span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000;">1.</span></strong></span><span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000; text-decoration: underline;"> <a href="http://rboot.co/R3YpJg" target="_blank">14 new laws for 2014</a></span></strong></span><br />
<br />
<span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000;">2. </span></strong></span><span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000; text-decoration: underline;"><a href="http://rboot.co/R3ZKzN" target="_blank">A new poll says Illinoisans are not happy with Speaker of the House Rep. Michael Madigan</a></span></strong></span><br />
<br />
<span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000;">3. </span></strong></span><span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000; text-decoration: underline;"><a href="http://rboot.co/1n6ZcUW" target="_blank">How do ballot measure signatures get to Springfield?</a></span></strong></span><br />
<br />
<span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000;">4. </span></strong></span><span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000; text-decoration: underline;"><a href="http://rboot.co/R404ys" target="_blank">Cartoon: Bigotry the dinosaur</a></span></strong></span><br />
<br />
<span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000;">5. </span></strong></span><span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #ff0000;"><strong><span style="color: #ff0000; text-decoration: underline;"><a href="http://rboot.co/1dQdQiX" target="_blank">Want to tell your elected officials what you think about the laws in your area? Use our Sound Off tool. </a></span></strong></span> ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1464944/thumbs/s-US_UK_CA-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/aj-walkley/bowls-of-love-an-intervie_b_5243052.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Bowls of Love: An Interview With Author and Health Coach Ali Rakowski]]></title>
      <author>A.J. Walkley</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/aj-walkley/bowls-of-love-an-intervie_b_5243052.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:23:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Growing up with your friends and peers, it's never quite clear which path we all will end up taking in our lives. Oftentimes we lose track of some of these people as we get older (though Facebook makes that harder to do these days). One of my childhood friends from as far back as my Girl Scout days recently reconnected with me over social media and, as a writer myself, I was excited to learn that she had aspirations to write a cookbook. Ali Rakowski, health coach and soon-to-be author, is now taking to Kickstarter to fund her very first Paleo soup-based cookbook. I took the opportunity to sit down with Ali and find out more about her own path to this amazing project.<br />
<br />
<strong>A.J.:</strong> How did you first get into healthy eating and cooking? <br />
<br />
<strong>Ali:</strong> I have always loved the idea of cooking since I was a little girl. My mom almost always cooked a homemade dinner, and I eagerly sat at the kitchen island on my favorite stool watching her every move. I was (and still am) a big klutz, so I typically was only allowed to help with boring tasks like setting the table. Luckily, I observed carefully and finally started to do some creative cooking in dorm rooms in college, and then really expanded my cooking capabilities after college when I had a real kitchen.<br />
 <br />
<strong>A.J.:</strong> Tell me a little bit about your project, <em>Bowls of Love</em>? <br />
<br />
<strong>Ali:</strong> <em>Bowls of Love</em> is a seasonal soup cookbook that will feature around 50 original Paleo recipes. Paleo, for those who aren't familiar, is a modern adaptation of the diet of Paleolithic humans (sometimes referred to as "The Caveman Diet"). The Paleo diet includes grass-fed pasture-raised meats, wild fish, eggs, fruits, vegetables, nuts and unprocessed oils; it excludes grains, dairy, legumes, soy, refined sugar and processed food. While this book is perfect for any grain/gluten-free, lactose intolerant, experienced Paleo eater or anyone looking for fresh and easy nutritious recipes, it is much more than a collection of recipes. <em>Bowls of Love</em> highlights my philosophy that cooking is the most pure and simple way to share love. There is no easier (or better) way to nourish the people in your life than by feeding them a healthy, beautiful, delicious meal. Feeding the people in my life is always a celebration, a promotion of good health, a gesture of appreciation and generosity and most importantly a gateway to conversation. All relationships are built and sustained through communication, and sharing a meal every day with the ones that you love acts as the perfect catalyst.<br />
<br />
<center><a href="http://images.huffingtonpost.com/2014-04-30-SoooPaleo261HighRes.jpg"><img alt="2014-04-30-SoooPaleo261HighRes.jpg" src="http://images.huffingtonpost.com/2014-04-30-SoooPaleo261HighRes-thumb.jpg" width="380" height="570" /></a></center><br />
<strong>A.J.:</strong> Why did you want to focus your cookbook on soups? <br />
<br />
<strong>Ali:</strong> I have always loved cooking soups and I got especially hooked on the process while working remotely for two years. Being away from my great coworkers was not an easy task, so I made myself busy with a new hobby of cooking Paleo recipes. I would wake up early and chop all the veggies and then let my soup simmer on the stove all day while I was working. A fresh bowl of steamy, hot soup was the perfect end to any day when I was cold, sick, tired or just needing some TLC.<br />
 <br />
<strong>A.J.:</strong> You're collecting bowls for this project. How did this idea arise? <br />
<br />
<strong>Ali:</strong> When talking to my best friend Mallory about the book, she helped me come up with the idea of asking all my favorite people for a bowl. I reached out to family, friends and loved ones and asked them to send me a bowl - any shape, size or design that they wanted. I am now dedicating each recipe in the book to one person and the recipe will be photographed in the bowl from that person. The entire experience of requesting the bowls, hearing responses and then receiving the bowls in the mail has been incredible beyond words. I seem to be getting a mystery package in the mail almost every day - bowls have come from France, Germany, New York, Florida, Nashville and loads of places in between. Every single bowl is a reminder of the love and support that I have in my life, and now I have the opportunity to share this positive energy with the world through my cookbook.<br />
 <br />
<strong>A.J.:</strong> What do you hope to get out of your Kickstarter campaign for <em>Bowls of Love</em>? <br />
<br />
<strong>Ali:</strong> I am absolutely thrilled to have my project on Kickstarter. I have backed crowdfunding projects before, and I think it is a fantastic way for creative projects and businesses to come to life with the help of people everywhere. Along with being a cookbook writer, I am a health coach, so I am incredibly passionate about helping other people achieve a holistic sense of health and wellness. My hope is that the Kickstarter campaign will encourage people to recognize the importance of nourishment, both for themselves and others. If this campaign helps one person start cooking who otherwise wouldn't, I will consider it a success. Selfishly, I also think that launching my project on Kickstarter will be an amazing opportunity to connect and reconnect with people past and present in my life that are interested in going on this journey with me.<br />
<br />
<center><a href="http://images.huffingtonpost.com/2014-05-01-SoooPaleo213HighRes.jpg"><img alt="2014-05-01-SoooPaleo213HighRes.jpg" src="http://images.huffingtonpost.com/2014-05-01-SoooPaleo213HighRes-thumb.jpg" width="383" height="570" /></a></center><br />
<strong>A.J.:</strong> Are you offering any donor goodies? <br />
<br />
<strong>Ali:</strong> Of course! There will be everything from recipe postcards and signed copies of the cookbook, to private cooking lessons and cooking parties! The rewards will vary greatly so everyone who is interested will have the opportunity to participate.<br />
 <br />
<strong>A.J.:</strong> Is there anything else you'd like potential donors to know? <br />
<br />
<strong>Ali:</strong> I want the donors to know that their assistance with funding this cookbook will help fulfill a longtime dream of mine and will help ensure that hundreds or thousands (or millions!) of people will have more knowledge around how to cook and eat healthy while enjoying their food and not breaking the bank. Whether you are Paleo, gluten-free, dairy-free or just a plain old regular eater that wants something new and interesting to serve on the table, this book is for you. There is so much love and excitement exploding out of this venture and nothing but good things can from that!<br />
<br />
<strong>If you're interested in participating in the <em>Bowls of Love</em> Kickstarter campaign, learn more about it <a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/alirak/bowls-of-love-paleo-soups-for-the-seasons" target="_hplink">here</a>.</strong> ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1464944/thumbs/s-US_UK_CA-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/loren-kleinman/protostar-braxton-cosby_b_5254541.html</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Protostar: An Interview with Braxton A. Cosby]]></title>
      <author>Loren Kleinman</author>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/loren-kleinman/protostar-braxton-cosby_b_5254541.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 18:19:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-award-winning author Braxton A. Cosby is a dreamer who evolved from concepts on pen and paper to pixels and keyboards. He tells stories that evoke emotions and stimulate thought. <em>Protostar: Book 1 The Star-Crossed Saga</em> and <em>The School of Ministry: The Windgate </em>are currently two young adult series he created. Braxton is also the CEO of the full-service entertainment company Cosby Media Productions, which has five divisions including film, television, music, print media and consultative services. Braxton lives in Georgia with his wife, three children and a troop of crazy African Cichlids.<br />
<br />
<strong>Loren Kleinman (LK): Your personal mission is to "change lifestyles." How do you relate to writing Young Adult fiction? </strong><br />
<br />
Braxton Cosby (BC): I think changing lives is an aspect of everything I do. Or at least that's what I'm trying to incorporate. I feel that I have been called to bring healing -- not just through my job as a physical therapist, but also in the words I write. I feel a huge responsibility has been given to me with my platform, and I want to use my books and writings as a vehicle to convey positive messaging to people of all ages. My love for young adult books and for young people in general is an inspiration. I want to tell stories that are not just unique, but are tales that become more of an experience that people part take in when they read. <br />
<br />
<strong>LK: Can you talk about your background in physical therapy and how that influences your writing?</strong><br />
<br />
BC: I love what I do daily as a physical therapist. I am able to touch the lives of so many people on a daily basis. I hear their personal stories and provide encouragement and hope in the midst of circumstances that force them to adapt and survive. My writing becomes a reflection of that because I incorporate the "survival" theme in most of my stories and show characters that adapt over time, and pursue accomplishing mutual goals against insurmountable odds. <br />
<br />
<strong>LK: You're the nephew of Bill Cosby. I mean we had to bring that up, right? What's your relationship like? How has he been supportive of your writing? And do you consider it a blessing or a curse?</strong><br />
<br />
BC: Uncle Bill is an amazing inspiration for me. He has accomplished so much over his career and the most important thing he has done is touch the lives of millions. I did a book tour with him in the past, and to see hundreds of people come up to him and tell him how important all the projects he's done were to them and their families is awe-inspiring. I want my books, movies and music to do the same thing. They have to mean something to me first, and then I know they will touch others. I've turned down projects based on propaganda alone. His God-given talent for storytelling has thankfully matriculated down to me. I am able to infuse detail into my world-building which brings readers out of the present. Uncle Bill also encourages me to be the best 'me' that I can be and to not be afraid to follow my own path, in spite of what the norm is. The shadow of being a Cosby is so much more than a blessing. It gives me opportunities to have conversations and meet people that I would've otherwise not been able to connect with. Now, with my company Cosby Media Productions in full swing, we are developing intellectual properties in partnership with fabulous people who share our vision. <br />
<br />
<strong>LK: Can you talk about your upcoming release, <em>Protostar</em>? How did you come up with the title and the premise? </strong><br />
<br />
BC: <em>Protostar </em>is a young adult love story, wrapped in a sci-fi backdrop that tells the story of two star-crossed lovers brought together by fate and destined to be torn apart. William, a bounty hunter and prince from his home planet Fabricius, is sent to Earth on a mission to kill a star-child (a humanoid being that will inherit the powers of the Sun) named Sydney, before she tears the solar system to pieces. When he arrives on Earth, the assassination is delayed three days due to unforeseen circumstances and he decides to shadow her in hopes to find out more about his target. But, he makes the mistake of getting too close to her over time which creates an internal struggle, forcing him to choose between love and duty. There's a great mix of twists and turns, fantastic action, large set pieces, and memorable characters. We've already gone into film production, completing the screenplay and initial casting. <br />
<br />
<strong>LK: You're a busy (I mean busy) man. Can you talk about how you manage your time with so much on your plate?</strong><br />
<br />
BC: I have a great team of players behind me. It starts with home. My wife helps me manage the family and we set aside time for each other and then I get to work. Then there's the business side. With Cosby Media Productions (CMP), Leon, my COO, does a wonderful job of coordinating calls and connecting us with people and businesses for productive partnerships that we feel are setting the stage for getting our projects off the ground in major ways. <br />
<br />
<strong>LK: You were nominated by <em>Jezebel Magazine</em> as one of the 50 Most Beautiful Atlantans, not only for your looks, but for your dedication to service in the community and beyond. Can you share with us your philosophy on community service and how that also relates to the writing community? </strong><br />
<br />
BC: It was a great honor bestowed upon me by <em>Jezebel Magazine</em>. I have a lot of respect for the magazine and the growth they've accomplished here in the Southeast. I love that the "50 Most" achievement went beyond recognizing people for just their looks. I understand the importance of community service, not just to those within the same community with similar backgrounds, but with the entire community of the world. With the birth of social media, people can now be reached across distance in mere microseconds. I get so many people reaching out to me and thanking me for my timely statements, articles, quotes and tweets on social media. I'm so humbled that I can be used as a vessel to encourage others. It extends well beyond just my blog, Cosby's Corner, where I talk about everything from movies, books, film and current projects. Not to mention the health advice and information I share on the "Ask The Fat Doctors" radio show on WAOK. <br />
<br />
<strong>LK: What's your take on the rise in author bullying on Amazon and other venues like Goodreads?</strong><br />
<br />
BC: I can't believe that something this petty is happening, especially in a venue as important as reading and writing. Egos and attitudes always seem to get in the way of progress. The rise of indies in both print and film/television is putting the pressure on higher-ups and the consumers are now gravitating to good content in opposition to good marketing. I love the current climate and environment we're living in right now, minus the garbage. <br />
<strong><br />
LK: If you could spend a day with any one of your characters in <em>Protostar </em>who would it be?</strong><br />
<br />
BC: It would be William. He's the daring, brave, good-looking, unconventional hero who is in transition. I appreciate people who are willing to not be afraid of change and accept the idea that the way they think the world needs to exist might be the wrong way of thinking. His character reflects the power of truth and of course love, which I feel is the most powerful force in the universe. Obviously, with <em>Protostar </em>being just the first book in the series, we will continue to see William grow and struggle to accept the things he cannot change and allow love to guide his thought processes going forward. <br />
<br />
<strong>LK: If I give you a time machine, what time period and in what place would you travel to?</strong><br />
<br />
BC: The future! I love the advancements that man has made over time. Although we still have our laundry list of issues, I believe the best form of man is yet to come. We are slowly learning more and more how to appreciate other's differences and developing a tolerance for individuality. At the base of humanity, there is a need to feel loved, appreciated and accepted. Everyone deserves a chance to experience all of these. No matter what you may feel about someone and their choices, maintaining the ideal of love will always help in positioning opportunities for positive exchanges and decision-making that will further the growth of our society. ]]></description>
      <enclosure url="http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1464944/thumbs/s-US_UK_CA-mini.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
