<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Vox -  All</title>
  <subtitle/>
  <icon>http://cdn3.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52517/voxv.png</icon>
  <updated>2014-05-01T12:40:09-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.vox.com/rss/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T12:40:09-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T12:40:09-04:00</updated>
    <title>55 colleges under investigation on sexual assault</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://cdn1.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/32406827/161326467.0_standard_400.0.jpg" /&gt;



  

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/cards/campus-sexual-assault-title-ix/55-colleges-are-under-education-department-investigation-for-how-they"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/cards/campus-sexual-assault-title-ix/55-colleges-are-under-education-department-investigation-for-how-they</id>
    <author>
      <name>Libby Nelson</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T12:30:10-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T12:30:10-04:00</updated>
    <title>Jobs Day is coming tomorrow — here's what you should know</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://cdn1.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/32406377/146170699.0_standard_400.0.jpg" /&gt;



  &lt;p&gt;Friday at 8:30 AM eastern time, the Bureau of Labor Statistics will release its monthly Employment Situation Report. In other words, it's &lt;a href="http://www.vox.com/cards/jobs-day-the-employment-situation-report-release-is-awesome/jobs-day-the-employment-situation-report-what-is-it"&gt;Jobs Day!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll have the numbers for you when they're available. For now, the context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On April 30, the Commerce Department reported an &lt;a href="http://www.vox.com/2014/4/30/5667806/why-economic-growth-ground-to-a-halt-last-quarter"&gt;awful GDP number for the first quarter of the year&lt;/a&gt;. The report could have had a silver lining if it had convinced the Federal Reserve to do more to help the economy. But l&lt;span&gt;ater that day the Federal Reserve decided to keep their policies &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vox.com/2014/4/30/5668278/the-economy-has-nearly-stopped-growing-but-the-fed-is-staying-the"&gt;exactly the same&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, arguing that there are signs the economy picked up late in the quarter after a bad winter and that the labor market keeps improving.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new jobs numbers will help us see whether that was a huge mistake or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reuters' poll of economists is &lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2014/04/29/us-usa-economy-employment-idUSBREA3S0YB20140429"&gt;expecting&lt;/a&gt; 210,000 net new &lt;a href="http://www.vox.com/cards/jobs-day-the-employment-situation-report-release-is-awesome/seasonal-adjustments"&gt;seasonally adjusted&lt;/a&gt; jobs for April. If we hit that, or if we come close and see upward revisions to the February and March numbers, then everything will look fine. But if we fall short of expectations or see downward revisions to the past two months, then it's going to look like the Fed made a big error by standing still in the face of a weak quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5671288/jobs-day-is-coming"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5671288/jobs-day-is-coming</id>
    <author>
      <name>Matthew Yglesias</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T12:10:10-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T12:10:10-04:00</updated>
    <title>You’re nearly eight times more likely to be murdered if you’re black</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://www.vox.com/chorus_images/32385157/standard/rss_large/1398916202" /&gt;



  &lt;p&gt;There's another indicator of racial disparity in the United States: murder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blacks are nearly eight times as likely and Hispanics are more than twice as likely to die from homicide as whites, according to &lt;a href="http://www.vpc.org/studies/hispanic.pdf"&gt;a new study&lt;/a&gt; from the Violence Policy Center. For blacks, the rate is near &lt;a href="http://www.vox.com/2014/4/21/5636412/countries-most-homicides-deadliest-murder-rates"&gt;the 25 countries and territories&lt;/a&gt; with the highest homicide rates in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Murder_rate_by_race" class="photo" src="http://cdn2.vox-cdn.com/assets/4387111/murder_rate_by_race.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of these minority victims were also nearly twice as likely to be young (24 and younger) as white victims.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Homicide_victims_24_and_younger" class="photo" src="http://cdn2.vox-cdn.com/assets/4387223/homicide_victims_24_and_younger.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Homicide, in fact, was the leading cause of death in 2010 among blacks aged 15 to 24, and the second leading cause of death among Hispanics in the same age range. In comparison, homicide ranked as the number three leading cause of death for American Indians and Alaska natives 15 to 24 and number four for whites and Asians and Pacific Islanders 15 to 24.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rate and age breakdown of homicides are not the only differences between various racial and ethnic groups: blacks and Hispanics were also much more likely to die as a result of gun violence than any other group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Homicide_victims_killed_by_firearms" class="photo" src="http://cdn1.vox-cdn.com/assets/4387135/homicide_victims_killed_by_firearms.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hispanics are also much more likely to die in the hands of strangers than either black or white victims.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Homicide_victims_killed_by_strangers" class="photo" src="http://cdn3.vox-cdn.com/assets/4387371/homicide_victims_killed_by_strangers.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what explains these racial disparities? The report offers little speculation or clues as to why. But part of the problem, at least for Hispanics, could be related to gang violence. The report found 30 percent of Hispanic homicide victims die in gang-related killings, compared to 11 percent of black victims and 4 percent of white victims.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;q class="right" aria-hidden="true"&gt;There's also socioeconomic issues that can't be detached from the issues of homicide, gangs, and gun violence&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's also socioeconomic issues that can't be detached from the issues of homicide, gangs, and gun violence. Minorities and young people face &lt;a href="http://www.pbs.org/newshour/bb/unemployment-rates-higher-young-people-minorities/"&gt;considerably higher unemployment rates&lt;/a&gt;. They're often discriminated against in &lt;a href="http://www.vox.com/2014/4/30/5665778/americas-real-racism-problem-doesnt-look-like-donald-sterling"&gt;subtle ways&lt;/a&gt;. They're more likely to fall into &lt;a href="http://www.vox.com/2014/4/24/5647660/boys-incarcerated-fathers-school-behavior-prison-pipeline"&gt;a cycle of crime and imprisonment&lt;/a&gt;. And they often live in segregated areas with &lt;a href="http://obs.rc.fas.harvard.edu/chetty/website/v2/Geography%20Executive%20Summary%20and%20Memo%20January%202014.pdf"&gt;little opportunity to move up the economic ladder&lt;/a&gt;. How all these issues interact is of &lt;a href="http://www.rand.org/content/dam/rand/www/external/labor/seminars/adp/pdfs/adp_ajph.pdf"&gt;major concern&lt;/a&gt; to researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Violence Policy Center analyzed federal data, some of which is unpublished, for its findings. It cautions, however, that there's one big caveat to the data: the total number of Hispanic victims might be too low, since government agencies often report data on race but not ethnic origin. That matters because Hispanics sometimes identify their race as separate from their ethnic origin, meaning some of them consider themselves white or black as far as race goes but Hispanic in terms of ethnic origin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Given the faulty data, the report calls on government agencies to improve how they collect and report information for Hispanic victims. That might help provide a clearer view of the problem — and how to solve it.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5670296/youre-nearly-eight-times-more-likely-to-be-murdered-if-youre-black"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5670296/youre-nearly-eight-times-more-likely-to-be-murdered-if-youre-black</id>
    <author>
      <name>German Lopez</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T12:00:14-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T12:00:14-04:00</updated>
    <title>'You're all slaves': Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu rants against smart phones</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://cdn2.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/32404691/476825887.0_standard_400.0.jpg" /&gt;



  &lt;p&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, in the news lately for his harshly critical views of &lt;a href="http://www.vox.com/cards/israel-palestine/palestinian-unity-deal"&gt;the new Palestinian unity government&lt;/a&gt;, has found something else to condemn, albeit jokingly: smart phone users. Netanyahu, sounding a bit like American comedian &lt;a href="http://gawker.com/louis-c-k-s-explanation-of-why-he-hates-smartphones-is-1354954625"&gt;Louis CK&lt;/a&gt;, teased reporters about their smart phones as they snapped photos of him just before a press conference. Here's the video, &lt;a href="http://www.timesofisrael.com/netanyahu-rants-against-smartphones/#ixzz30TH1QJjJ"&gt;flagged by&lt;/a&gt; Times of Israel reporter Adiv Sterman:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe frameborder="0" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/zLVnpqdmuKM" height="525" width="700"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I don't get this new world. Everybody's taking pictures," he said, pantomiming photo-taking. "When do they have time to do live? Only taking pictures, that's all they do."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If you didn't take a picture, it's like you never actually lived it. I lived and didn't take a pictured," he said, switching between Hebrew and English, a bit of code-switching common in Israel. He concludes, "So I'm the only person here without all these electronic devices. And I'm a free man and you're all slaves. You're slaves to your gadgets. You're slaves."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously Netanyahu was just joking, in the way that anyone of his generation in any country is apt to do. Still, it may not shock you, after watching this video, to learn that Netanyahu's party has not exactly been scoring home runs with the Israeli youth vote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Israel's latest national election, in January 2013, Netanyahu's right-wing Likud party did retain its lead, but it lost share among youth voters as part of a larger shift in Israeli politics. Young right-leaning Israelis &lt;a href="http://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-21088844"&gt;moved&lt;/a&gt; in large numbers from Likud to &lt;a href="http://www.thetimes.co.uk/tto/news/world/middleeast/article3646233.ece"&gt;support&lt;/a&gt; the far-right Home Party, a nationalist and pro-settler party that is attempting to pull Netanyahu to the political right and opposes negotiations with Palestinians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously Israeli youth did not switch their political allegiance because Netanyahu doesn't take selfies, but the point is that there is a growing disaffection with Netanyahu's party among young Israelis, who are not excited about Netanyahu, and that's a part of a larger and actually-significant change in Israeli politics.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5671590/youre-all-slaves-israeli-prime-minister-netanyahu-rants-against-smart"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5671590/youre-all-slaves-israeli-prime-minister-netanyahu-rants-against-smart</id>
    <author>
      <name>Max Fisher</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T11:10:08-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T11:10:08-04:00</updated>
    <title>Get ready for a future where antibiotics no longer work</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://cdn3.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/32402189/16880.0_standard_400.0.jpg" /&gt;



  &lt;p&gt;The world could soon be headed for a "post-antibiotic era" — in which many of our best drugs don't work and common infections can kill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That was the terrifying conclusion of the World Health Organization's&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.who.int/drugresistance/documents/surveillancereport/en/"&gt; first report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; on the growth in drug-resistant microbes around the world. Worst of all, the report notes, we don't even have the proper monitoring around the globe to fully assess the situation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;q aria-hidden="true" class="right"&gt;the microbes are coming, and we don't have the drugs to treat them&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Resistance to common bacteria has reached alarming levels in many parts of the world," the report said, "indicating that many of the available treatment options for common infections in some settings are becoming ineffective."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what is going on here? Microbes, including bacteria, fungi, and viruses, have been &lt;a href="http://www.cdc.gov/getsmart/antibiotic-use/antibiotic-resistance-faqs.html#prevent-infections"&gt;developing resistance&lt;/a&gt; to our drugs for quite some time now. Let's say someone has pneumonia and takes an antibiotic. The drug kills &lt;i&gt;most&lt;/i&gt; of the pneumonia bacteria — but a few survive. Those survivors live on and multiply, producing more drug-resistant bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This process has been happening for all kinds of microbes, including those that cause gonorrhea, pneumonia, urinary tract infections, tuberculosis, malaria, and HIV. &lt;span&gt;Overuse of antibiotics in both people and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a style="background-color: #ffffff; line-height: 1.5;" href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/wonkblog/wp/2013/12/14/the-fda-is-cracking-down-on-antibiotics-at-farms-heres-what-you-should-know/"&gt;in livestock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; has drastically accelerated resistance and made it much, much worse.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we had enough new drugs coming, maybe that would be okay. But that's not the situation. Both technical hurdles and lukewarm financial incentives means that there &lt;a href="http://www.cdc.gov/features/AntibioticResistanceThreats/index.html"&gt;aren't enough drugs&lt;/a&gt; coming down the pike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The overall picture doesn't look good — but the urgency varies from microbe to microbe. Some microbes are getting to the point where we need ever more expensive drugs to provide a second or third line of defense. Other microbes, meanwhile, have developed strains that are resistant to all of our drugs, period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Without urgent, coordinated action by many stakeholders, the world is headed for a post-antibiotic era, in which common infections and minor injuries which have been treatable for decades can once again kill," said Keiji Fukuda, WHO's Assistant Director-General for Health Security, in a &lt;a href="http://www.who.int/mediacentre/news/releases/2014/amr-report/en/"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Some pneumonia is becoming resistant to what's usually the last line of treatment available&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Screen_shot_2014-04-30_at_6.32.02_pm" class="photo" src="http://cdn2.vox-cdn.com/assets/4386045/Screen_Shot_2014-04-30_at_6.32.02_PM.png"&gt;&lt;i&gt;K. pneumoniae&lt;/i&gt; is a bacteria that causes many hospital-acquired infections, including some forms of pneumonia. "The high proportions of resistance to 3rd generation cephalosporins reported for &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;K. pneumoniae&lt;/i&gt; means that treatment of severe infections likely to be caused by these bacteria in many settings must rely on carbapenems, the last-resort to treat severe community and hospital acquired infections. These antibacterials are more expensive, may not be available in resource-constrained settings, and are also likely to further accelerate development of resistance."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Gonorrhea is becoming resistant to the treatment of last resort, too&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Screen_shot_2014-04-30_at_6.36.54_pm" class="photo" src="http://cdn3.vox-cdn.com/assets/4386069/Screen_Shot_2014-04-30_at_6.36.54_PM.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In &lt;i&gt;N. gonorrhoeae&lt;/i&gt;, finally, decreased susceptibility to third-generation cephalosporins, the treatment of last resort for gonorrhoea, has been verified in 36 countries and is a growing problem."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span&gt;Drug-resistant tuberculosis is spreading&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Screen_shot_2014-04-30_at_5.27.28_pm" class="photo" src="http://cdn1.vox-cdn.com/assets/4386149/Screen_Shot_2014-04-30_at_5.27.28_PM.png"&gt;Multidrug-resistant tuberculosis (&lt;a href="http://www.cdc.gov/tb/publications/factsheets/drtb/mdrtb.htm"&gt;MDR-TB&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;span&gt;is resistant to the two most potent treatments available, a&lt;/span&gt;lthough that doesn't mean that it's completely untreatable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;In 2010, 17 percent of people with multiple drug-resistant TB in Africa died&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Screen_shot_2014-04-30_at_7.02.09_pm" class="photo" src="http://cdn3.vox-cdn.com/assets/4386157/Screen_Shot_2014-04-30_at_7.02.09_PM.png"&gt; This was the highest death rate in the 2010 data set among the regions studied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;So what would a post-antibiotic era look like?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;q class="right" aria-hidden="true"&gt;without Antibiotics, one in six HIP REPLACEMENT patients would die&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's easy to forget what the world was like before the first antibiotic was discovered in 1928. Diseases like pneumonia and simple scrapes and infections could often cause death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, antibiotics have become indispensable for modern medicine — they're used for surgeries, transplants, kidney dialysis. Without antibiotics, giving birth would be much more dangerous. Without antibiotics, an estimated one in six &lt;span&gt;hip replacement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;patients would die.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The short story is that we really, really don't want this to happen. You can read more about what the post-antibiotic world would look like in Maryn McKenna's story &lt;a href="https://medium.com/editors-picks/892b57499e77"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Can we avoid a "post-antibiotic" future?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The WHO doesn't say that a full "post-antibiotic era" is inevitable, but that it's "a very real possibility." So here's what people can do to prevent it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="align-right"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="align-right"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;q class="right" aria-hidden="true"&gt;take EVERY PILL in YOUR PRESCRIPTION&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because antibiotic overuse is the main problem here, you should &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; take antibiotics that have been prescribed to you by a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there's a twist: when you &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; prescribed antibiotics, you should take all of them — every last pill. While it might seem sensible to stop taking the pills when you feel better, it increases the chances that bacteria are still alive in your body and will survive and multiply, spreading their resistance to future generations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors and farmers, for their part, need to only use antibiotics when needed and explore how to prevent infections in the first place. (For example, a simple checklist was able to reduce line infections from 11 percent to zero at one hospital — Atul Gawande has the full story in the New Yorker &lt;a href="http://www.newyorker.com/reporting/2007/12/10/071210fa_fact_gawande?currentPage=all"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.) And policymakers need to figure out how to get new antibiotics into research and development. Because&lt;span&gt;, one way or another, we're going to need new drugs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5669526/get-ready-for-a-future-where-antibiotics-no-longer-work"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5669526/get-ready-for-a-future-where-antibiotics-no-longer-work</id>
    <author>
      <name>Susannah Locke</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T11:00:12-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T11:00:12-04:00</updated>
    <title>Think the US-Mexico border is dangerous? Migrating to Europe is much deadlier</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://cdn2.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/32401397/53139639.0_standard_400.0.jpg" /&gt;



  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There's a human rights crisis on (and just off) the shores of Europe. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;q aria-hidden="true" class="right"&gt;about 20,000 migrants have died en route over the past 20 years&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thousands of migrants from the Middle East, Africa, and Central Asia are boating across the Mediterranean in an attempt to enter the European Union — and hundreds of them are dying. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Last fall, a ship &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/comment/2013/10/lampedusas-migrant-tragedy-and-ours.html" target="_blank"&gt;caught on fire and killed 300 migrants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; a mile from European shores. About 20,000 migrants have died en route over the past twenty years, according to the International Organization for Migration.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crossing the Mediterranean is much deadlier than crossing from Mexico into the US. The National Foundation for American Policy found that the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://fusion.net/justice/story/us-mexico-border-deaths-increasing-report-17996"&gt;deadliest year on record&lt;/a&gt; for the US/Mexico crossing was 2012, when 477 migrants were killed. In 2011, which was the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.unhcr.org/4f27e01f9.html"&gt;deadliest year for the Mediterranean crossing&lt;/a&gt;, over three times as many migrants were killed: at least 1,500.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;This map from the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2014/04/30/illegal-immigration-by-boat-a-dangerous-but-common-way-of-entering-europe/" target="_blank"&gt;Pew Research Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; shows that these migrants aren't mainly coming from the African countries that border the Mediterranean. They're often coming from places in crisis, like Syria, Mali, and Afghanistan, and crossing several countries by land before sailing to Europe — typically to Lampedusa, an island owned by Italy that's closer to Africa than the European mainland — on one of the world's deadliest migrations by sea:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://cdn1.vox-cdn.com/assets/4385099/Screen_Shot_2014-04-30_at_2.28.04_PM.png" class="photo" alt="Screen_shot_2014-04-30_at_2.28.04_pm"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fact that so many migrants are coming from war-torn countries like Syria makes what ultimately happens to many of them even more heartbreaking. Many migrants crossing the Mediterranean hope to apply for asylum once they arrive in Europe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, and many of them might have legitimate claims that they're fleeing danger and persecution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="align-left"&gt;
&lt;img src="http://cdn0.vox-cdn.com/assets/4385357/183651204.jpg" class="photo" alt="183651204"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Survivors of the 2013 shipwreck off Lampedusa. Tullio M. Puglia/Getty&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;B&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;ut when they're on the boat, they don't have legal status, and Frontex, the European equivalent of the U.S. Border Patrol, is supposed to "push back" any migrant boats they can get to before the migrants arrive on European shores.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Mediterranean crossing can be deadly, especially in the not-always-seaworthy boats used by traffickers. And because the job of Frontex is to push migrants back, it's come under attack for not doing more to keep them safe. Survivors of the boat fire from last fall &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dw.de/former-lampedusa-migrant-nobody-helped/a-17143269" target="_blank"&gt;allege&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that they saw multiple helicopters circle above them, but no one came to their rescue until they were discovered by Italian fishermen five hours after the boat sank. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At least in America, Border Patrol officers who see &lt;a href="http://www.cbp.gov/newsroom/local-media-release/2014-04-28-000000/del-rio-border-patrol-agents-rescue-salvadoran-mother" target="_blank"&gt;people drowning in the Rio Grande&lt;/a&gt; rescue them before "processing" and deporting them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5668916/think-the-us-mexico-border-is-dangerous-migrating-to-europe-is-much"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5668916/think-the-us-mexico-border-is-dangerous-migrating-to-europe-is-much</id>
    <author>
      <name>Dara Lind</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T10:50:11-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T10:50:11-04:00</updated>
    <title>How Chicago is using psychotherapy to fight crime — and winning</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://cdn3.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/32400811/obama_bam.0_standard_400.0.jpg" /&gt;



  &lt;p&gt;The idea of preventing crime using psychotherapy may sound vaguely utopian. But, believe it or not, it works, the White House is starting to take notice, and two researchers have a plan to take it nationwide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The basics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The program in question is called Becoming a Man (BAM), and was developed by the nonprofits Youth Guidance and World Sport Chicago for use in Chicago schools. BAM consists of weekly hour-long sessions with groups of no more than 15 high school boys (the average instructor-student ratio is 1 to 8). It's not therapy in the strictest of senses, but the overall approach is borrowed from cognitive-behavioral therapy (CBT), which has overtaken more Freudian approaches in recent decades among practitioners and has a &lt;a href="http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0272735805001005"&gt;large&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs10608-012-9476-1#page-1"&gt;research base&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0304395998002553"&gt;demonstrating&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.campbellcollaboration.org/lib/download/143"&gt;its effectiveness&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe width="650" height="366" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/mJHHjBRA7zQ" frameborder="0"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CBT is all about teaching meta-cognition: thinking about thinking. In a pure therapy setting, that means teaching patients to identify thought patterns that contribute to depression, anxiety, and so forth, so that they can work to replace them with healthier patterns. For example, a common negative thought pattern is catastrophizing, or exaggerating the importance of a short-term negative event in a way that causes undue distress and overreaction; if you've ever gotten a small piece of negative feedback from your boss and within a few minutes started worrying that you're about to get fired, that's catastrophizing in action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BAM is interested in tackling catastrophizing, but of a very particular sort. The operating theory is that living in distressed and dangerous neighborhoods leads teen boys to adopt certain behaviors automatically that are totally rational and adaptive in that context, but fail them in an academic setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In distressed, high-crime areas where sources of formal social control, like police or schools, are overwhelmed, people are on their own. People in this circumstance learn to automatically push back when threatened to avoid additional victimizations in the future," the University of Chicago's Jens Ludwig and Anuj Shah &lt;a href="http://www.hamiltonproject.org/papers/think_before_you_act_new_approach_preventing_youth_violence_dropout/"&gt;note&lt;/a&gt;. "If a teenager hears a teacher say, 'Sit down and be quiet,' the youth might instinctively or automatically perceive this as a situation where he should retaliate, act up, and preserve his reputation."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that in mind, BAM uses its sessions to identify and challenge particularly common and harmful automatic thought patterns like that. Here's one example, from Ludwig and Shah:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Program staff divide students into pairs. One student is told he has thirty seconds to get his partner to  open his fist, then the exercise is reversed. Physical force is almost always the preferred method to compel counterparts to open their hands. After the exercise, the group leader asks the youths to explain what they tried and how it worked, pointedly noting that (as was commonly the case) almost no one simply asked his partner to open his fist. When asked why, youths would frequently say, "He wouldn’t have done it" or "He would have thought I was a punk," to which the group leader would respond by asking, "How do you know?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exercise serves two purposes: First, it is an experiential way of teaching students about hostile attribution bias, or the instinctive assumption that the other person has negative intent; second, it helps engage some who would not normally sign up for a prosocial activity by subversively showing them that beyond getting to skip an academic class, the very first activity of the program involves sometimes-rowdy horseplay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How we know it works&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div align="center"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Youthguidance" class="photo" src="http://cdn3.vox-cdn.com/assets/4389087/youthguidance.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Obama sits in on a BAM session on February 15, 2013. Photo courtesy of Youth Guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three randomized controlled trials — one of the &lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/lets-stop-guessing-whether-a-bill-will-work-instead-lets-test-it/2012/12/07/903396f2-3d64-11e2-bca3-aadc9b7e29c5_story.html"&gt;best methods available&lt;/a&gt; for testing if a policy works — have been conducted of BAM so far. The &lt;a href="http://www.nber.org/papers/w19014.pdf?new_window=1"&gt;first trial&lt;/a&gt;, by Sara Heller, Harold Pollack, Roseanna Ander, and Ludwig (all at the University of Chicago), was conducted with 2,740 male Chicago students in grades 7-10 in 2009. It also included an after-school component where students learned non-traditional sports requiring considerable focus and self-control (archery, handball, martial arts, etc.), which was meant to hammer home the points made in school. It found that participants in BAM had 44 percent fewer violent crime arrests, and 38 percent fewer arrests for other charges that year. School outcomes improved too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="http://crimelab.uchicago.edu/sites/crimelab.uchicago.edu/files/uploads/Plus%20results%20brief%20FINAL%2020130802.pdf"&gt;second trial&lt;/a&gt;, conducted by Heller with the city of Chicago in 2012, combined the program with summer jobs placements for high schoolers, and had a sample of 1,634 students, both male and female. This confirmed the effects of the program on violent crime, with arrests falling by 51 percent during the program, and the fall lasting beyond its end. The &lt;a href="http://www.nber.org/papers/w19862"&gt;third trial&lt;/a&gt;, which was conducted in the 2012-2013 school year with a sample of 106 students in grades 9-10,  and added in academic remediation to the mix, found that course failures fell by 66 percent during the program year and absences by 25 percent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;q aria-hidden="true" class="center"&gt;participants in BAM had 44 percent fewer violent crime arrests&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings weren't positive across the board. The second trial didn't share the positive academic findings of the first or third, and the first trial didn't find that the effects of BAM on crime continued after students left the program. And because of the program's relative youth, we still have a lot of time before we'll know if any of its effects last into adulthood. That said, Ludwig tells me he and the other authors committed to tracking participants for years into the future to figure out exactly that. "Chicago has electronic rap sheets, so we can follow arrest rates forever," he explains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What it costs — and what it pays back&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the most striking finding from the randomized trials is that BAM quite possibly pays for itself many, many times over. In the first trial, BAM cost $1,100 per participant, but the authors estimated its effects could save society as much 30 times that by reducing violent crime and its attendant social costs in the year the program takes place. By comparison, the Perry preschool study, the most famous and impressive trial in that area, had &lt;a href="http://heckman"&gt;benefits exceeds costs&lt;/a&gt; by a factor of between 19 and 31, if you count future benefits the same as present-day ones. That, Ludwig says, "looks good compared to any intervention the government can consider, including early childhood, and yet we're seeing it with a target population that lots of people have written off."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Different variations on the program vary in cost, however. The second trial cost $3,000 per participant, and the third trial cost $4,400 per participant — a fourfold increase. Then again, those trials incorporating additional elements like a summer jobs program and remediation programs. And if the 30-1 benefit cost ratio is anywhere close to right, then it's worth doing even given a dramatic increase in the program's cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Where to go from here&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Christianchampagne" class="photo" src="http://cdn1.vox-cdn.com/assets/4389103/christianchampagne.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="caption"&gt;President Barack Obama enters the East Room of the White House with BAM participant Christian Champagne at the start of the "My Brother's Keeper," event, Feb. 27, 2014. Photo courtesy of Peter Souza/White House.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The program has attracted national attention before. President Obama, who was &lt;a href="http://www.whitehouse.gov/the-press-office/2014/02/27/remarks-president-my-brothers-keeper-initiative"&gt;introduced&lt;/a&gt; to BAM by his former chief of staff and Chicago mayor Rahm Emanuel, &lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/chicago-teens-stories-on-becoming-a-man-leave-a-mark-on-the-president/2014/02/09/8808c336-82b8-11e3-9dd4-e7278db80d86_story.html"&gt;sat in on a session&lt;/a&gt; in February 2013, and &lt;a href="http://www.whitehouse.gov/photos-and-video/photo/2013/06/president-obama-talks-students-bam"&gt;invited participants&lt;/a&gt; to the White House that July. When he announced his My Brother's Keeper Initiative, which targets young men of color, he was introduced by &lt;a href="http://www.whitehouse.gov/photos-and-video/photo/2014/02/president-obama-enters-east-room-christian-campagne"&gt;Christian Champagne&lt;/a&gt;, an 18-year-old BAM veteran. "I could see myself in these young men," Obama said. "And the only difference is that I grew up in an environment that was a little bit more forgiving, so when I made a mistake the consequences were not as severe."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But so far, there hasn't been much movement to expand the program nationwide. Ludwig and Shah are hoping to change that. In a &lt;a href="http://www.hamiltonproject.org/papers/think_before_you_act_new_approach_preventing_youth_violence_dropout/"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; for the Hamilton Project, they They propose allocating $400 million over five years to competitive program that would select forty cities, in each of which a local nonprofit would offer the program to 500 youths. The plan would also include having Youth Guidance, the original developer, run versions of it in ten of the selected cities, so researchers can see if BAM can be "franchised" out to other organizations without becoming less effective; if it can, the prospects for succeeding nationally are much higher. If the demonstration works, Ludwig and Shah support allocating $2 billion a year to make the program available nationally; that's enough to include every youth in poverty, and a few above the poverty line too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's still a lot about the program that's unknown. We don't know if the same model can work with girls, or how large, if existing at all, effects outside the program period will be. But it does put another nail in the coffin of the old conventional wisdom that &lt;a href="http://www.nationalaffairs.com/doclib/20080527_197403502whatworksquestionsandanswersaboutprisonreformrobertmartinson.pdf"&gt;"nothing works"&lt;/a&gt; when it comes to using health services and education to prevent crime, a conventional wisdom that contributed to &lt;a href="http://www.vox.com/cards/everything-prisons-reform-incarceration-criminal-justice/why-has-the-prison-population-increased-in-the-last-30-years"&gt;policies ramping up incarceration&lt;/a&gt;, with all the &lt;a href="http://www.pewtrusts.org/uploadedFiles/Collateral_Costs.pdf"&gt;attendant&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.newyorker.com/arts/critics/atlarge/2012/01/30/120130crat_atlarge_gopnik?currentPage=all"&gt;damage&lt;/a&gt; that causes. "The persistent skepticism in the '70s about social policy preventing crime," Ludwig says, "might turn out to be too pessimistic."&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5669578/how-chicago-is-using-psychotherapy-to-fight-crime-and-winning"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5669578/how-chicago-is-using-psychotherapy-to-fight-crime-and-winning</id>
    <author>
      <name>Dylan Matthews</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T10:10:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T10:10:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Who is Mark Fields? A primer on Ford's next CEO</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://cdn0.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/31948677/462921605.0_standard_400.0.jpg" /&gt;



  &lt;p&gt;Mark Fields, currently Ford's Chief Operating Officer, will be the car company's next CEO, the company announced on the morning of May 1. Fields is taking over from Alan Mulally who led the company through bankruptcy and made Ford the only US automaker to avoid a government bailout and partial takeover during the financial crisis. Fields will start running the company on July 1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ford today is a different beast from the loss-plagued company Mulally took over in 2006. Here is a Vox primer on who Fields is and what he could bring to the corner office.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Who is Mark Fields?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fields has been at Ford since 2002, when the company moved him away from then-Ford-controlled Mazda. Fields moved up through the ranks at Ford, and since December 2012 has been Ford's Chief Operating Officer. The COO is responsible for a company's day-to-day operations, keeping the CEO apprised of things like production and what lower-level managers are saying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Whom is he replacing?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fields will replace Alan Mulally, who has been the CEO since 2006, when Ford recruited him from Boeing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mulally is &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://articles.latimes.com/2012/apr/15/business/la-fi-books-20120415"&gt;widely credited&lt;/a&gt; with turning the company around after it posted massive losses in the mid-2000s. The company lost $30.1 billion from 2006 to 2008, according to &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2012/11/01/ford-ceo-mulally-succession-fields/1673779/"&gt;USA Today&lt;/a&gt;, but made most of that money back in the following years. In 2010, the company brought in $6.6 billion, its &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2011/01/28/ford-2010-profit-hits-hig_n_815269.html"&gt;biggest profit&lt;/a&gt; in more than a decade. That allowed Ford to avoid both the bankruptcy and the unpopular federal bailouts that competitors GM and Chrysler needed during the financial crisis (though Mulally &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://finance.yahoo.com/blogs/daily-ticker/bailouts-gm-chrysler-were-good-ford-too-alan-113859133.html"&gt;has said&lt;/a&gt; that the bailouts benefited Ford as well).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of Mulally's success was in the culture change he instituted at the company, as well as redesigning cars to make them more fuel-efficient and cutting lines like Jaguar, Land Rover, and Mercury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mulally has remained successful as CEO; in 2013, Ford pulled in $7.2 billion, leading Ford to give Mulally a &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://money.cnn.com/2014/03/07/news/companies/mulally-stock-pay/"&gt;$13.8 million performance bonus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Why does it matter?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it was rumored earlier this year that Microsoft wanted to steal Mulally away from Ford, he was adamant that he would not leave the company. And it looked like he would stay after Microsoft named Satya Nadella CEO.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moreover, it matters because Mulally has become synonymous with the Ford turnaround. His departure is the end of an era at the automaker and would give Fields some big shoes to fill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Fields has plenty of experience, with more than two decades of it at Ford or Ford-owned companies. Before he was COO, Fields was executive vice president and president of The Americas at Ford. Ford's executive chairman, Bill Ford, had in the past credited Fields with helping to &lt;a href="http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2012/11/01/ford-ceo-mulally-succession-fields/1673779/"&gt;save the company&lt;/a&gt; by revamping Ford's North American business.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/2014/4/21/5636974/who-is-mark-fields-a-primer-on-fords-next-ceo"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/2014/4/21/5636974/who-is-mark-fields-a-primer-on-fords-next-ceo</id>
    <author>
      <name>Danielle Kurtzleben</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T09:20:08-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T09:20:08-04:00</updated>
    <title>It's International Workers' Day, here's the case for higher pay</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://cdn3.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/32396173/487582917.0_standard_400.0.jpg" /&gt;



  &lt;p&gt;Today is May 1, aka International Workers Day in most developed countries, though not a holiday here in the United States. The kind of tacky workers-versus-owners politics that goes into May Day celebrations certainly cuts against the grain of American political culture, where even our off-brand Labor Day in the autumn doesn't have much of an edge to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But in reality this kind of class politics has rarely been more relevant in the USA. Workers have been taking it on the chin for almost fifteen straight years now and it's hurting the overall economy. A raise would do us all some good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a look at this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://cdn1.vox-cdn.com/assets/4388581/labor_share.png" class="photo" alt="Labor_share"&gt; That's the labor share of overall national income, and it's been on a pretty steady path of decline for about fifteen years now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course on its own that doesn't tell you very much. Lots of extremely rich people receive labor income, and lots of middle class people are shareholders in companies. But an &lt;a href="http://www.oecd.org/els/soc/OECD2014-FocusOnTopIncomes.pdf"&gt;OECD report&lt;/a&gt; out this week clarified usefully that, yes, non-labor income is primarily the province of the very rich:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align="center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://cdn0.vox-cdn.com/assets/4388589/Screen_Shot_2014-05-01_at_7.46.34_AM.png" class="photo" alt="Screen_shot_2014-05-01_at_7.46.34_am"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You see that for the top 0.1 percent and the top 0.01 percent, business income and capital income are really really important. Down in the bottom 99 percent, people are working for a living. So the decline in the labor share is bad for the vast majority of people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course there's more to life than distribution. Maybe workers are getting a smaller slice of a rapidly growing pie? But of course that hasn't been the case:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://cdn1.vox-cdn.com/assets/4388605/growth.png" class="photo" alt="Growth"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since 2000, our strongest growth year was 2004 when we achieved 3.8 percent GDP growth. The economy grew faster than that in 1997, 1998, 1999, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; 2000 and only a tiny smidge smaller in 1996. It also grew faster than that in 1983, 1984, and 1985. It grew faster than that four different times in the 1970s and six different times in the 1960s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theory was that policies friendly to capital would increase business investment, and thus help spur broadly beneficial growth. But it hasn't exactly worked out that way. Profits have soared while investment has stayed much more restrained:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://cdn3.vox-cdn.com/assets/4388621/fredgraph.png" class="photo" alt="Fredgraph"&gt; The result is a stalled economy. Money is collecting in the coffers of successful companies that don't want to spent it on expansion or being flushed out as dividends or share buybacks to people who own stock — mostly rich people who mostly don't have immediate economic needs they need to meet. On an individual basis, this makes sense. Executives want to try to maximize profits and shareholders want to try to maximize payouts to themselves. But collectively it's a disaster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If average people had more money in their pockets, they would buy more iPads and dinners out with the family and new super-blenders  and gym memberships and movie tickets and all the rest. That kind of enhanced consumer buying power would create the opportunity for more business investment to actually pay off, driving a cycle of higher investment and more growth. Today with profits sky-high and interest rates super-low, companies aren't constrained in their investment by financial considerations but by objective opportunities. If people don't have any money, there's no reason for companies to invest in making stuff to sell to them. A higher wage economy wouldn't be literally better for every single person but it would be broadly beneficial not just for wage-earners but for the overall business and growth climate.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5671056/its-international-workers-day-heres-the-case-for-higher-pay"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/2014/5/1/5671056/its-international-workers-day-heres-the-case-for-higher-pay</id>
    <author>
      <name>Matthew Yglesias</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2014-05-01T09:19:32-04:00</published>
    <updated>2014-05-01T09:19:32-04:00</updated>
    <title>A great map of the states people want to flee</title>
    <content type="html">  
  &lt;img alt="" src="http://www.vox.com/chorus_images/32396083/standard/rss_large/1398950365" /&gt;



  

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.vox.com/2014/4/30/5668588/illinois-connecticut-maryland-gallup-interstate-migration-rates"/>
    <id>http://www.vox.com/2014/4/30/5668588/illinois-connecticut-maryland-gallup-interstate-migration-rates</id>
    <author>
      <name>Danielle Kurtzleben</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
